<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ExpandableLayout</string>
    <string name="UsageOne">RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="UsageTwo">ListView</string>
    <string name="UsageThree">SimpleUse</string>

    <string name="ezreal">Ezreal – the Prodigal Explorer </string>
    <string name="ezreal_label">Primary role : Marksman (ADCarry)  \nSecondary role : Mage (Mid)</string>
    <string name="ezreal_story">The intrepid young adventurer Ezreal has explored some of the most remote
        and abandoned locations on Runeterra. During an expedition to the buried ruins of ancient Shurima,
        he recovered an amulet of incredible mystical power. Likely constructed to be worn by one of the Ascended,
        the enormous talisman nonetheless fit snugly upon his arm, amplifying his raw sorcerous skill to
        such an extent that he\'s gained the reputation of a hero, much to his embarrassment.</string>
    <string name="jinx">Jinx - the Loose Cannon</string>
    <string name="jinx_label">Primary role : Marksman (ADCarry)  \nSecondary role : N/A</string>
    <string name="jinx_story">Jinx lives to wreak havoc without a thought for consequence, leaving a trail
        of mayhem and panic in her wake. A manic and impulsive criminal, she despises nothing more than boredom,
        and gleefully unleashes her own volatile brand of pandemonium to the one place she finds dullest: Piltover.
        With an arsenal of deadly toys, she unleashes the brightest explosions and loudest blasts - all the better
        to shock and surprise the hapless authorities. Always just out of the law\'s reach, Jinx\'s favorite game
        is to toy with Piltover\'s finest - especially Vi \n Piltover had long been known as the City of Progress,
        a place where peace and order reigned. That serenity was challenged when a new kind of criminal arrived,
        the likes of whom had never been seen. This mysterious outlaw unleashed a series of warped and destructive
        capers that endangered the entire city, and left its people reeling from the worst crime spree in Piltover\'s history.</string>
</resources>
